The oddest friends are about to get even
The Other Woman is a comedy, romance film directed by Nick Cassavetes.
After discovering her boyfriend is married, Carly soon
meets the wife he's been cheating on.
And when yet another affair is discovered, all three women team up
to plot mutual revenge on the three-timing SOB.
Carly Whitten, played by Cameron Diaz.
Kate King, played by Leslie Mann.
Amber, played by Kate Upton.
Mark King, played by Nikolaj Coster-Waldau.
Frank, played by Don Johnson.
Lydia, played by Nicki Minaj.
The Other Woman is a 2014 American romantic comedy film
directed by Nick Cassavetes, written by Melissa K.
Stack, and starring Cameron Diaz, Leslie Mann, Kate Upton, Nikolaj
Coster-Waldau, Nicki Minaj, Taylor Kinney, and Don Johnson.
The film follows three women—Carly (Diaz), Kate (Mann), and Amber (Upton)—who
are all romantically involved with the same man (Coster-Waldau).
After finding out about each other, the trio take their revenge on him.
Development of The Other Woman began in January 2012, when 20th Century Fox hired Stack to write
the script, based on the original idea from the 1996 comedy The First Wives Club.
Casting was done between November 2012 and June 2013.
Filming began on April 29, 2013, in locations including Manhattan, Long Island, the Hamptons, Dockers Waterside
Restaurant on Dune Road in Quogue, and the Bahamas, and it concluded on August 27 that year.
Aaron Zigman composed the score and LBI Productions produced the film.
The film was released on April 25, 2014, in the United States,
and distributed worldwide by 20th Century Fox.
The film received mostly negative reviews from critics, but was a box
office success, grossing $196.7 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of infidelity, revenge, unfaithful
boyfriend, extramarital affair, unfaithful husband.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.